ここ　タリスマン·サルーンで語られる物語は
Here at Talisman Saloon, we only discuss the affairs of others.
全て　ひとごと
いいですかな レモネードキャンディ
All right, Lemonade Candy?
ＯＫ
Okay.
私の友達が　今すごく困ってて
One of my friends is in quite a bind right now.
だからその子のことを話したいの タリスマン
So I'd like to talk about her, Talisman.
よろしいですとも
Of course!
それでは　聞かせてください
Then, please tell me about the concerns your friend is facing.
あなたのお友達がどのような悩みを抱えているのか
タリスマン
Talisman!
その子はね
After she graduated from school,
she immediately started a tough job.
卒業してすぐに大変な仕事に就いて
責任重大で
A job carrying a lot of responsibility.
でも　それはいいの
But that's not the problem.
その子も後悔はしてないはず
I'm sure she doesn't regret it.
なるほど
I see.
困ってるのは人間関係なのかな
What she's in a bind about is, I suppose, her work relationships.
その職場で部下っていうか　先輩っていうか
At her work, she has this subordinate...
Or rather, a senior colleague...
ちょっと説明の難しい同僚がいてね
Anyway, she's got this colleague who is hard to describe.
仕事をやっていく上で彼のことを避けては通れないんだけど
There's no avoiding him when she's at work, but...
苦手なタイプなのですか
Is he the sort that she doesn't get along well with?
その人 やることがめちゃくちゃで
He does some crazy things.
でもね　正しいことを言ってるなって思うときもあるの
But there are times that she feels what he's saying is right.
だから　信用できるかなって思ったりもしたんだけど
So she thought she might be able to trust him at some point.
君のお友達はその同僚に幻想を見ていたのかもしれませんね
That sounds like it might be wishful thinking on your friend's part.
幻想なのかな
Do you think so?
まずは先入観を廃して
I think she needs to first discard this
preconception and then face his true character.
ありのままの彼と向き合ってみる必要があるんじゃないかな
お友達にはそうアドバイスしてあげたらどうだろう
Why don't you give this advice to your friend?
うん
Okay.
迷える人々の悩ましき日々をこのタリスマンめにお聞かせください
Please share with me, Talisman,
the difficulties experienced by those adrift.
答えは常にあなたの物語の中に隠れています
The answer is always hiding inside your story.
ありのままの彼と向き合うか
Face his true character, huh?
Dare ni mo miserarenai mono
My head is full of things
Atama no naka afurete
That I can never tell anybody of
In this perfect world
Machigai sae mo nai sekai he
I roam, a lost being
Mayoikonderu
Arienai hodo surikomareteru
This world is impossibly hard on me
It's an illusion that plays out before my eyes
Me ni mieru mono dake no "sekai" genshou
Abakidaseru kana
Can I find its faults?
Plastic tac tic
Plastic, all is plastic
Mou dare mo okashiku narenai yo
Nobody is allowed to be insane
Kisama mo plastic beautiful world
You're made of plastic too, like this beautiful world
In this beautiful world
Utsukushi sugiru sekai ni
Boku wa nazeka
There is something
Hikari ga mienakute
That obscures all light for me
Haretsu shite yuku kokoro ga
My heart tries to break out
And finds no answer
Mugen no rifurekushon
Secret kills for you
Secret remains for you
The secret remains for you
Don't show me a dark future
Misekake no iro to
Mirai wo abakanai de
Nor a world of pretense
Keep it secret motion
Keep our motion secret
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 翼叔   校对:西西   后期:时末
#04: Nobody Knows Your Mask
狡噛のことが聞きたいのかい
Do you wanna ask me about Kougami?
分かりますか
You can tell?
あんた あいつと妙に縁があるからな
You two have this strange connection. Almost like fate.
あの人にどう接していいのか いまだに分からないんです
I still don't know how I should deal with him.
もっと理解しろっていう人もいますし
Someone told me I should try to understand him better.
同じ人間だと思うなと言われたこともあります
And someone else told me not to think of him as human like us.
Oh, that must've been Inspector Ginoza.
そっちは宜野座監視官のせりふだな
あいつらしい
It's just like him.
犬は犬　飼い主は飼い主
Dogs are dogs. Owners are owners.
その一線を踏み越えない関係
I think that's where you need to draw the line.
それがお嬢ちゃんにとって一番だと思うね
It's best if you stay on one side and keep him on the other.
狡噛を理解するってのはな
To understand Kougami means to think the way he does.
狡噛のようにものを見て 狡噛のように考えるってことだ
To see the world through his eyes.
それができるようになったとしたら
And if you do that, your Psycho-Pass will become like his as well.
そのときあんたのサイコパスは狡噛と同じ数字をたたき出してることだろうよ
深えんをのぞくとき
"When you gaze long into an abyss, the abyss also gazes into you."
深えんもまたこちらをのぞいている
狡噛はな　闇を見詰め過ぎたんだ
Kougami stared into the darkness for too long.
そして 今でもまだ見詰め続けてる
And he's still staring into it even now.
あいつにとって　世界でたった一つの正義ってやつは
Maybe for him, the only true justice in the world
その闇の奥底にしかないんだろう
exists solely in the depths of that darkness.
そんなものをお嬢ちゃんもやつと一緒に探したいと思っているのなら
If you wanna go search for something like that with him,
俺にはもう何も言えない
there's nothing more I can say.
俺はあんたを止められないよ
I can't stop you.
コウのときもそうだった
I couldn't stop Ko, either.
それって
Is that—
事件かい
Did something happen?
みたいです
Looks like it.
俺と六合塚は非番なんでな
Kunizuka and I are off duty,
狡噛と縢で頼むぜ
so go with Kougami and Kagari.
で　いったい何事だ
So what's going on?
ホームセキュリティーの一斉点検で
The comprehensive home security inspection
この部屋のトイレが２カ月前から故障していたことが分かった
showed that the toilet in this apartment
has been broken for the past two months.
なのに住人からの苦情が一切ない
However, the resident hasn't filed a single complaint.
それで管理会社が不審に思い通報してきたんだそうだ
So the management company
became suspicious and reported it to us.
葉山公彦 ３２歳 独身 無職
Hayama Kimihiko, thirty-two years old. Single. Unemployed.
無職って いるんですか 今どきそんな人
Unemployed? Do people like that exist in this day and age?
口座を洗ってみたが
I checked his bank account.
こいつはアフィリエイト·サービス·プロバイダーから
He's receiving lots of compensation from an affiliated services provider.
多額の報酬を受け取っている
暮らしには何一つ不自由なかっただろう
He probably lived in great comfort.
Well, if you can make tons of
money just by being popular on the net,
ネットの人気者ってだけでがっぽり稼げるんなら
そりゃ外に出て働くのもバカらしくなるわな
of course you'd think it'd be stupid to go outside and work.
どこかで長期の旅行中とか
Could he have gone on a trip somewhere?
ないな
No. When a person leaves their apartment, it leaves a record on the street scanners.
部屋の外に出れば 街頭のスキャナーに記録が残る
この街で何の痕跡も残さず遠出をするのは至難の業だ
In this town, it's virtually impossible to travel without leaving any trace.
そもそも口座からの引き落としも２カ月間途絶えている
Besides, his bank account hasn't had
any withdrawals for the past two months.
死んでるな　葉山は
Hayama is dead.
だね 殺される方が消えるより簡単
Yep. Getting killed is easier than disappearing.
結論を出すのが早いぞ
It's too soon to come to a conclusion.
この部屋の内装ホロ 再起動できるか
Is it possible to restart the interior Holo of this room?
ちょっと待て
Hold on a minute.
あれ　これは
Oh?
ホログラフの椅子には座れない
You can't sit on a Holography couch.
だから　普通はホロと本物の位置を同期させる
So normally, the position of the Holo
object is synced with the real world one.
そこの長椅子 本当はこの位置にあったはずだ
That couch must've been here originally.
それを誰かが動かした
But someone moved it.
なるほどね
I see.
せーの
こいつを隠したかったんだろうな
They must've wanted to hide this.
こんな小さな傷がどうした
Why bother covering such a small scratch?
鑑識ドローンにスキャンさせろ
Have a Crime Lab Drone scan it.
やっぱりだ　テープの跡だな
I knew it. Residue from adhesive tape.
どういうことだ
What does that mean?
この部屋の中から葉山公彦を
It's the secret behind the magic trick
that they used to make Hayama Kimihiko
影も残さず消しちまった手品の種さ
disappear from this place without a trace.
まずは絞殺か毒殺、電気ショックの心臓まひでもいい
He could've been strangled, poisoned,
or maybe they stopped his heart with an electric shock.
出血のない方法で犠牲者を殺し
Either way, first they killed the victim in some bloodless manner.
それから 部屋にビニールシートを敷いて
Then they spread a plastic sheet
over the room and dismantled the body
遺体を細切れに分解する
風呂やトイレの排水溝から流せる程度にまで粉々に
into pieces small enough to fit down the bath or toilet.
おそらく殺す段階で抵抗されたんだろう
Hayama probably resisted when they tried to kill him.
床に傷が残り
It left a scratch on the floor,
それから ビニールシートを固定したときのテープの跡も残しちまった
and traces remained of the adhesive tape they used to put down the plastic sheet.
度胸と根性はあるが
They had the guts and the willpower, but this was the work of amateurs.
素人の殺しだな
まさか
You serious?
征陸のとっつあんなら この程度
If old Masaoka were here,
部屋に踏み込んだ途端に嗅ぎ当てるぜ
he'd have sniffed out something like this
the moment he stepped into the room, Gino.
ギノ　猟犬の嗅覚をなめるなよ
Don't underestimate a hunting dog's sense of smell.
下水管の血液反応をチェックしてみろ
Check the sewer pipe for traces of blood.
話はそれからだ
We can discuss this further after that.
分かった
Okay.
開いたよ
We're in.
葉山がネットで使っていたアバターは…こいつか
So this is the avatar that Hayama was using on the net.
アフィリエイトで食っていけるんだから
He must've been quite popular to have made a living as an affiliate.
相当な人気者だったんでしょうね
タリスマン
Talisman...
何
What?
私　けさ
This morning... I...
このアバターと会ってます
met this avatar.
そんなわけで
So, thanks to the hard work of our precious Crime Lab Drones,
うちのカワイイ鑑識ドローンが頑張った結果
葉山さんちの排水溝からはめでたく遺体の断片が見つかりました
we successfully found the body pieces that were flushed from Mr. Hayama's residence.
はーい 拍手
Now, applaud!
なのに 誰かがネット上で葉山のコミュフィールドを運営し
And yet, someone's operating Hayama's CommuField on the net
葉山のアバターでうろつき回ってると
and hanging around using Hayama's avatar.
正解
Correct.
怪談だね
It's like a horror story.
成仏できずにネットをさまよう幽霊ってか
A ghost that remains chained to this
world, endlessly wandering the net, huh?
誰かが成り代わってるのか
Is someone assuming his identity?
どうだかね
I don't know.
葉山は失踪する以前から ふざけ半分に偽装ＩＰを使ってたみたい
It seems that even before Hayama went missing,
he was screwing around using fake IPs.
アクセスルートの追跡は
Have we tried tracking the access routes?
試してみてもいいけどさ
I can give it a shot, but they're going
through proxy servers that are clearly suspicious.
何か明らかにうさんくさいプロクシサーバを経由してるからね
まあ間違いなく逆探知対策は講じてるだろうね
They're undoubtedly taking steps to hide their tracks.
下手に追跡掛けると先方にも感づかれるよ
If we're not careful, they'll notice we're tracking them.
でもさ　少なくとも葉山のアバターを使ってるやつは
But, at least, the person who's using Hayama's avatar
自分が怪しまれているだなんてまだ気付いてないはず
should still think that they haven't aroused any suspicion yet.
それってチャンスなんじゃない
Doesn't that give us a chance?
ある意味　今回の容疑者は逃げも隠れもせずに
So, in a sense, the suspect this time isn't hiding or running away,
目の前をほっつき歩いているわけだ
but is walking around right in front of us.
うまく誘導すれば
If we play our cards right, we might be able
to get him to reveal clues that lead to his real identity.
正体をつかむ手掛かりになるようなぼろを出すかもしれない
よし やつのアバターに接触してみよう
Okay. Let's get in touch with Hayama's avatar.
手としちゃ悪くないが
That's not a bad idea...
誰がやる
But who's gonna do it?
なるほど
I see... So this person who's pretending to be Talisman
今タリスマンに成り済ましている偽者は
本物と遜色ない手際でこのコミュフィールドを２カ月間運営しているわけか
has been operating this CommuField as capably as the real owner for the past two months, huh?
興味深いな
How interesting.
宜野座さん　あれです
That's him, Inspector Ginoza.
どうやらよそのコミュフィールドに移動するみたいですね
Looks like he's going to another CommuField.
よし 追うぞ
Okay. Let's follow him.
スプーキーブーギーのコミュフィールドですね
Looks like this is Spooky Boogie's CommuField.
ここもかなりの大手ですよ
This is a big community too.
スプーキーブーギー
Spooky Boogie!
すてき
How lovely!
Spooky Boogie!
気を付けてくださいね
Please be careful.
ここの管理人アナーキストで有名なんです
The operator of this place is a famous anarchist.
刑事だってバレたら厄介なことになるかも
If she finds out we're detectives, there might be trouble.
葉山は タリスマンとは交流があるのか
Does she have any connections with Hayama... With Talisman?
そりゃどっちも有名ですし…
Well, both of them are famous, so she might.
いや　中の人が顔見知りかどうかは別ですけど
But whether the actual people know each other or not is a different story.
アクセスログを洗おう
Let's check their access logs.
お互いが相手のコミュフィールドに頻繁に出入りしているようなら…
If they often visit each other's CommuFields...
Hm? Tsunemori?
常守？
H-Hm? Inspector Ginoza?
あれ？宜野座さん？
ようこそ レモネードキャンディさん
Welcome, Miss Lemonade Candy.
私はこのコミュフィールドのホスト スプーキーブーギー
I'm Spooky Boogie, the host of this CommuField.
What?!
ちょっと珍しいお客さんだから
Since you're quite the unexpected visitor,
チャットルームにお招きしたの
I invited you to my chat room.
ご迷惑だったかしら？
I'm not troubling you, am I?
いや　あの　その…私なんかをどうして
Um, not really... But why me?
噂には聞いてたけど
I've heard rumors, but you really don't realize
how famous you are, do you, Lemonade Candy?
あなたって本当に自分がどれだけ有名人か自覚してないのね
レモネードキャンディ
それとも　常守朱さんって呼ぶべきかしら
Or should I call you Miss Tsunemori Akane?
あなた　もしかして…
Could you possibly be...
まあ　私の正体は卒業アルバムとでもにらめっこして捜してごらんなさい
Well, if you wanna know who I am,
why don't you look through your graduation album or something?
うまく当てたら
If you figure it out, I'll treat you at our class reunion.
同窓会でおごってあげるわ
で　刑事課の監視官さまが私のコミュフィールドに何の用
So, what business does an Inspector
at the CID have with my CommuField?
どうにも遊びに来たふうには見えないんだけれど
Somehow I doubt you came just to hang out.
ええっと…あのね
Well...
Are you friends with Talisman?
あなた タリスマンとは懇意にしてる
そりゃまあね
Well, yeah, since we're rivals on the access ranking.
お互いアクセスランキングのライバル同士だし
あの人のフィールドやアバターに最近何か変わったところってない
Have you noticed anything different lately about his Field or avatar?
そう　ここ２カ月ぐらいの間に
Like, during the past two months?
そうね～最近はこれといって別に…
Let's see...
Nothing much lately.
むしろ２カ月前の方が彼　ちょっとどうかしてたと思わない
But don't you think he was acting strange before then?
えっ　そうだっけ
What? He was?
あのころのタリスマンってさ
Around that time, Talisman was speaking erratically.
空気読めない発言とか
He was also holding events that were clearly intended to get affiliate money.
露骨なアフィ稼ぎのイベントとかやらかして
結構アンチも増えてたじゃない
So the number of people who were anti-Talisman was growing, right?
古株の人気アバターもそろそろ落ち目かなってみんなで噂してたもんよ
We were saying how it looked like that popular old-timer was on his way out.
でも　今はそんなことないよね
But he isn't like that now, right?
ええ　今日も相変わらずクールでジェントルなタリスマン
Yeah. Talisman is his usual cool, gentle self today.
本人は心を入れ替えたとか言ってたけど
Although he said he turned over a new leaf,
一度落ち目になったアバターが持ち直すのって結構難しいんだけどね
it's quite hard for an avatar who
went into decline to make a comeback.
で　これって何かの捜査なの
So is this some sort of an investigation?
タリスマンが何かやらかした
Did Talisman do something?
まだ何とも言えないんだけど…
We still can't say anything,
どうにかしてタリスマンのアバターを使ってる本人を捜さなきゃならなくて
but we have to somehow find the
actual person using the Talisman avatar.
I see... That sounds kinda interesting.
何だか面白そう
ちょっと協力してあげようか？
Shall I give you a bit of assistance?
What?
公安局の幹部候補に恩を売っておくのも悪くないじゃない
It wouldn't be a bad idea to get one of the
Public Safety Bureau's rising stars in my debt, right?
アナーキストのスプーキーブーギーが…
Spooky Boogie, the famous anarchist, offering us help?
何だか意外
I didn't expect to hear that.
本音と建前ってやつよ
That's my public face and this is my private face.
同期のよしみもあるしね
We were in the same class, after all.
まあ　任せておいてよ
Well, leave it to me.
当フォーラムにお越しの皆さん
To those who came to my forum:
日頃からの感謝の意を込めて
私　スプーキーブーギーがささやかながらも宴の席を用意させていただきます
I, Spooky Boogie, will hold a modest party to show my appreciation.
来る４日の六本木オフ会にて
It'll be a meet-up in Roppongi on the 4th,
私の保持するホワイトクラウンを懸け
where I'll challenge my friend Talisman to a duel for the White Crown I hold.
わが友　タリスマンにデュエルマッチを申し込みます
オフ会？
A meet-up?
ええ 普段ネット上のコミュフィールドに集まっているユーザー同士が
Yes. The users who usually gather in a CommuField on the net
みんなでソーシャルネットでのアバターと同じホロコスをかぶって
hold a party wearing Holo-Cosplay that
matches their avatars on the social networks.
パーティーをするんです
妙なことを思い付くもんだな
They sure do come up with strange things these days.
で　そのイベントには間違いなくタリスマンも参加するのか
So are we certain Talisman will participate in the event?
あれで欠席したらタリスマンの人気はがた落ちです
With things the way they are,
his popularity will plummet if he doesn't show.
葉山公彦の代わりにタリスマンを演じているのが誰にせよ
No matter who's pretending to be Hayama Kimihiko,
あれだけ熱心にコミュフィールドの運営を続けてるんです
he's been enthusiastic enough about operating the CommuField
きっとオフ会にもタリスマンに成り済まして出てくるはずです
that I'm sure he'll show up there as Talisman.
どんなホロコスをかぶっていようと
No matter what Holo-Cosplay he's wearing,
そいつが執行対象になるだけの犯罪係数が計測できれば
if his Crime Coefficient indicates he's
a target for enforcement, the game is ours.
こっちのもんだ
で　場所は
So where will it be held?
六本木のクラブ　エグゾゼです
It'll be at Exoset, a club in Roppongi.
表は宜野座たちが 裏はドローンが固めている
Ginoza and the others are watching
the front, and Drones are at the back.
あとはやつが現れるのを待つだけだ
All we have to do now is wait for him to show up.
しかしこいつは…当世風の仮面舞踏会って趣か
So is this like a modern-day masquerade?
誰が誰だか分からない状況で
Don't these guys feel uneasy, cooped up in such a small place
こんな狭い場所に押し込められて
こいつらは不安じゃないのか
without knowing who the others really are?
匿名性を怖がってたら
You can't participate in social networks if you're afraid of anonymity.
ソーシャルネットなんてできませんよ
これはバーチャルじゃない
This isn't virtual.
殴れば血が出るし
If someone gets hit, they'll bleed.
ナイフ一つで命を奪えるリアルな空間だ
A single knife can take a life away. This is the real world.
なのに隣にいるやつの正体すら分からない
And yet, they don't even know who's right next to them.
正気の沙汰とは思えんな
They must be out of their minds.
そんな考え方してるからサイコパスが濁るんですよ
That kind of thinking is why your Psycho-Pass is so cloudy.
U-Um, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
あの ごめんなさい そんなつもりじゃ…
いや　まったくの正論だ
Well, it's hard to argue with that.
おい やつだ
Hey, it's him.
ここからじゃ狙えんな
We can't aim at him from here.
他の客が邪魔だ
The other partygoers are in the way.
私が接近してみます
I'll try getting closer to him.
「鎮圧執行システム　オンライン」
Suppression System, online.
嘘？
No way.
ホントだって
It's true.
あらら　やっぱりね
Oh, my. I knew it.
御堂さん？お察しのとおりです
Mido? You were right.
フロアでドミネーターの信号が出てる
A Dominator has been detected on the floor.
刑事が紛れ込んでますよ そこ
There's a detective in there somewhere.
やはりわなだったか…
So it really was a trap.
スプーキーブーギーめ
That damn Spooky Boogie...
もちろん逃げますよね
I trust you'll be making your escape?
捕まってもらっちゃ困りますよ
We can't afford for you to be captured.
こっちにだって まだやりたいことが残ってる
I have unfinished business too.
援護しますよ
Allow me to assist.
何だ こりゃ
What the hell is this?!
ホロコスへの同時ハッキングだ
All the Holo-Cosplays were hacked simultaneously!
本ボシが逃げるぞ
The real suspect will escape!
くそっ
Dammit! Let's use our Dominators!
ドミネーターだ
犯罪係数で被疑者を捜せ
Find the suspect by checking their Crime Coefficients!
うわっ　公安局だ
Ah! The cops are here!
Wait!
「犯罪係数　オーバー１１０」
Crime Coefficient is over 110.
「オーバー140　執行対象です」
Over 140. He's a target for enforcement action.
How many of them are there?
何人いやがる
期せずして一斉摘発ってわけか
So we ended up conducting a raid, huh?!
Oh, boy...
Damn. They got us.
やられた…
すっ　すまん
S-Sorry!
何だったんだよ 今日のオフ会は
What was up with today's meet-up?!
私の彼氏 公安局に捕まっちゃったじゃない
My boyfriend got captured by the Bureau!
どうしてくれんのよ
What're you gonna do about it!
み…みんな 落ち着いて
E-Everyone, calm down!
あれは公安局のガサ入れで 私は何の関係も…
That was a raid by the Bureau!
I had nothing to do with it!
嘘はよくないな スプーキーブーギー
You must not lie, Spooky Boogie.
騒ぎが起きたとき やつらは既にエグゾゼの中にいた
When the commotion started, they were already inside Exoset.
最初から主催者が手引きしていたとしか思えない
I can't help but think that the
organizer had guided them from the start.
これまでアナーキズムを掲げて皆に愛されてきたあなたが
You've preached anarchism all this time and been admired for it.
よりにもよって体制側の手先を務めるなど
And yet, you've acted as an agent for the government.
あってはならないことです
Such a thing is impermissible.
な…何を言ってるのよ
Wh-What're you saying?!
そもそも公安局に目を付けられるようなマネをしたのは
You're the one who did something to catch
the Bureau's eyes in the first place, Talisman!
タリスマン　あなたの方じゃない
あなたは自らのキャラクターを裏切った
You have betrayed your own character.
あなたはもうスプーキーブーギーではない
You are no longer Spooky Boogie.
皆に愛されるアバターとして立ち振る舞う資格はない
You are no longer qualified to be an avatar admired by the public.
D-Don't talk like you know everything!
あんたなんかに何が分かるってのよ
私はあなたのことをあなた以上に知っています
I know more about you than you yourself do.
ふ…ふざけないで
Q-Quit screwing around!
な…何よあれ　超キモい
Wh-What's with him? He's super creepy!
いったい何様のつもりよ
Who the hell does he think he is?!
あんなやつアクセス禁止にしてやるわ
I'm going to block his access.
二度と私のコミュフィールドには入れてやらない
I'm not gonna let him in my CommuField ever again.
その必要はないよ
There's no need for that.
君の方こそ もう二度とスプーキーブーギーになることはない
After all, you won't ever be Spooky Boogie again.
殺したのかい
Did you kill her?
この女は スプーキーブーギーにふさわしくない
That woman was ill-suited to the role of Spooky Boogie.
だがスプーキーブーギーは消えてはならない
But Spooky Boogie should not disappear.
みんなに笑顔をもたらすために
She must continue to bring smiles to everyone's faces.
だからスプーキーブーギーを残してこの女だけを消す
Spooky Boogie shall remain in this world,
but the woman behind her will disappear without a trace.
跡形もなく完全に
ああ…君なら菅原昭子よりも完璧なスプーキーブーギーが務まるよ
Indeed.
You can play a perfect Spooky Boogie, better than Sugawara Shouko herself.
葉山公彦より完璧なタリスマンになれたようにね
Just as you became a perfect Talisman, better than Hayama Kimihiko.
Fearii teeru wa
It seems all fairy tales
Sakki shinda mitai
Are dead
Renga no byoutou de
In a hospital ward of brick stones
Umaku utaenakute
My voice is too coarse to sing
Kiri ni kemuru yoru
Outside in the foggy haze
Ukabe akai tsuki
A red moon glows
Hora mite watashi wo
Look at me
Me wo sorasanai de
Do not avert your gaze
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
Behind black bars
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I was born
Behind black bars
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
Akui no daishou wo negae
I wish there were a punishment for evil
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Always I need you
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Now, grant us justice
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Before chaos takes us all
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Namae no nai kaibutsu
Nameless beasts
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Nameless beasts
Namae no nai kaibutsu
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".